<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="C8_title">Recovering your wallet</string>
    <string name="C8_tagline">Find out how you can use a recovery phrase to load a pre-existing wallet on your device.</string>

    <string name="C8_p1">Recovering a wallet from a recovery phrase is usually fairly easy. Recovery phrases (sometimes also called mnemonics) use a standard called BIP39, which provides a common way to recover coins between different wallets. The usual pattern for backing up and recovering a wallet is the following:</string>
    <string name="C8_p2">1. We create a wallet and the software provides us with either 12 or 24 words to write down and keep. The order of the words is important, so make sure you write them in the right order. In Padawan, you can see those 12 words at any time by going into the \"Recovery phrase\" screen in the menu.</string>
    <string name="C8_p3">In most other wallets, you will only get a chance to see those words once, SO MAKE SURE YOU WRITE THEM DOWN AND TREAT THEM LIKE THE MONEY THEY REPRESENT.</string>
    <string name="C8_p4">2. Upon creating a new wallet, you can always try to send a tiny amount of bitcoin to the wallet, delete the wallet, and attempt a full recovery using the words provided by the wallet. Alternatively, if you own two devices you can use for this test, you can try to create the wallet on one, recover it on a different device, and see the small amount you sent is accessible on both devices. If all goes well and you backed up your wallet correctly, you will be able to re-enter the recovery phrase, the exact same wallet will be generated, and the coins will be there.</string>
    <string name="C8_p5">3. In Padawan, you would click on \"I already have a Padawan wallet\" and enter your 12-word recovery phrase.</string>

    <string name="C8_h1">The power of recovery phrases</string>
    <string name="C8_p6">This ability to recover a wallet using only your words is very powerful, because it means that you don\'t actually need the wallet to be installed on your phone to transport your bitcoin. You can simply keep the 12 words somewhere safe (learning them by heart is also often useful, although you should not rely on that uniquely!) and rebuild a wallet later on when needed. Recovery phrases are also standard across many bitcoin wallets, which means you can rebuild a wallet using a different app or desktop wallet and the coins will be accessible!</string>
    <string name="C8_p7">This aspect of bitcoin software is often misunderstood and is worth taking the time to appreciate; bitcoins are not \"held\" in any mobile, desktop, or hardware wallet. They are simply accessed through them.</string>
    <string name="C8_p8">The signet coins you have on Padawan can be recovered and used on a range of other mobile, desktop, and hardware wallets that support BIP39 bitcoin wallets. If your recovery phrase is properly backed up, deleting the app on your phone is not an issue at all!</string>
</resources>
