<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="t2_h1">Bitcoin units</string>

    <string name="t2_p1">It is unfortunate but the word "bitcoin" has two completely different meanings. We speak of <i>Bitcoin</i> the network, the protocol, the open source project, and we also use the word "bitcoin" as one of the units of value when transacting on that network.
    </string>

    <string name="t2_p2">A bitcoin is a unit of value that can easily be broken down in smaller parts. Just like the kilometer can be broken down into meters and centimeters and the dollar can be broken down into quarters, dimes, and pennies, bitcoin can be broken into smaller units. And while there are many units to describe bitcoin, we believe only two of those to be important: the <i>bitcoin</i> and the <i>satoshi</i>. There are one hundred million (100,000,000) satoshis in a bitcoin.
    </string>

    <string name="t2_p3">100,000,000 satoshis = 1 bitcoin\n1 satoshi = 0.00000001 bitcoin</string>

    <string name="t2_p4">The symbols used to represent those units of value are not always the same. There is no central authority to dictate what should be the "official" symbol. Instead this choice is a matter of emergent consensus, and will eventually solidify over time around one symbol for each unit. Here are some of the symbols for bitcoin and satoshis you might see around in applications:
    </string>

    <!--  diagram symbols of bitcoin -->

    <!--  diagram symbols of satoshis -->

    <string name="t2_h2">Both units are useful</string>

    <string name="t2_p5">Depending on the size of a transaction, it is often more appropriate to think of the amount transacted as being in bitcoin or in satoshis. A brand new car might be worth 1.7 bitcoins (1,700,000,000 sats is not as easy for the eye to quickly understand), whereas a candy might be worth 250 satoshis (0.00000250 bitcoin is harder to read).
    </string>

    <string name="t2_p6">The ability to use both units is an important skill to develop. A lot of transactions are denominated in bitcoin, but their _network fee_ (tutorial #4) is almost always written in satoshis. You can switch between the two units in the main wallet display page by touching the bitcoin/satoshi symbol.
    </string>

    <!--  GIF of unit switch in wallet  -->
</resources>