<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--  string names for tutorials are defined as such:  -->
<!--  t1: tutorial 1  -->
<!--  h1: header 1  -->
<!--  p1: paragraph 1  -->

<resources>
    <string name="C1_title">What is the Bitcoin Signet?</string>

    <string name="t1_h1">What is the Bitcoin Signet?</string>

    <string name="t1_p1">Bitcoin networks are made up of thousands of computers across the world. These computers speak a common language and communicate directly with each other over the internet.</string>
    <string name="t1_p2">You might not know, but there are many bitcoin networks! They break into two families: the main network (there is only one of those) and the test networks (there are many of those!).</string>

    <string name="t1_h2">Mainnet</string>
    <string name="t1_p3">When people talk about "the bitcoin network", they usually mean the mainnet bitcoin network (or simply \"mainnet\").</string>
    <string name="t1_p4">The bitcoins on mainnet have monetary value, are used as money for transactions between people, and can be traded on cryptocurrency exchanges.</string>

    <string name="t1_h3">Test Networks</string>
    <string name="t1_p5">There are a few test networks, each with their own purpose. They tend to not be as well known as the mainnet network, but are very important nonetheless! Padawan uses the Signet network for its transactions, but you might also hear of Testnet3, Testnet4, and Regtest. The bitcoins on these networks are called signet/testnet/regtest coins and look and behave just like mainnet bitcoins. But unlike mainnet bitcoins, those test coins have no monetary value.</string>
    <string name="t1_p6">Test networks are used by software developers and organizations who create real-world applications that interact with bitcoin. These developers can use test networks to make sure their software is working properly before launching on mainnet. But you don\'t need to be a software developer to use them!</string>

    <string name="t1_h4">Padawan &amp; Signet</string>
    <string name="t1_p7">The signet and its coins are an invaluable resource for curious people to learn, play, and get confident with bitcoin networks before handling \"real\" mainnet bitcoins! Remember that test bitcoins DO NOT have monetary value.</string>
    <string name="t1_p8">Padawan will teach you the foundations of bitcoin, including making transactions and backing up wallets, all using the signet network. You cannot receive or send mainnet bitcoins to or from your Padawan wallet. Any coins you have on Padawan or send to friends using the app are signet coins with NO monetary value.</string>
    <string name="t1_p9">Use Padawan to learn, practice, and test the boundaries of your bitcoin knowledge!</string>
</resources>
