<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="C9_title">The different types of wallets</string>
    <string name="C9_tagline">Hot wallets, cold wallets, hardware wallets, mobile wallets… what you need to know to understand their uses.</string>

    <string name="t9_h1">
        Why is there more than one type of wallet?
    </string>

    <string name="t9_p1">The most important thing a bitcoin wallet does is secure a set of cryptographic keys (very big, very important numbers). Ensuring that these keys are not accessed by people other than the wallet owner is very important, and there is a range of solutions for this requirement that each have tradeoffs, often across the ease-of-use and security axes. Choosing the right wallet for a specific use case is important, and this chapter will help you understand why and when you might want to use different types of bitcoin wallets.</string>

    <string name="t9_h2">Hot vs cold wallets</string>
    <string name="t9_p2">The first distinction between wallets is whether they have any access to the internet at all. A wallet like Padawan is connected to the internet and is called a "hot wallet". This implies the attack surface for the wallet is bigger, and it has more ways it could "fail", but it makes it much easier to send and receive transactions. A hot wallet is perfect for holding small amounts of bitcoin for daily use (say the amount you would spend at a grocery store). A good analogy is a physical wallet you hold in your pocket with some cash in it. If it gets lost or stolen, you don\'t risk losing your savings, because those are held somewhere else safer (in a bank account for example).</string>
    <string name="t9_p3">Cold wallets often refer to small devices that do not ever have access or even know about the internet, or even the blockchain! They are often specialized pieces of hardware that can perform a very small range of tasks, namely to sign bitcoin transactions with keys they control. This makes them much more secure against attacks, but they also involve a bit more work when using them to spend or receive coins. Cold wallets are often used for storing larger amount of coins you don\'t need access to daily, similar to how you might go to the bank to get money for the week.</string>

    <string name="t9_h3">Hardware, software, mobile, lightning, custodial wallets</string>
    <string name="t9_p4">You might hear other names for wallets when searching for what best suits your needs (and remember that you can use many types of wallets for different uses!). The following are commonly used by people to interact with bitcoin:</string>
    <string name="t9_p5">1. Hardware wallet. Those are often small, specialized bitcoin devices that can be plugged in a computer or phone, but cannot use the internet. They would be considered in the family of "cold wallets".</string>
    <string name="t9_p6">2. Software wallet. When people speak of software wallets they often refer to applications you can use on your phone or desktop computer, and therefore those are often hot wallets. It is not a very good name, because all bitcoin wallets use software! But you\'ll encounter it enough that you should know what it means.</string>
    <string name="t9_p7">3. Mobile wallet. Mobile wallets are applications that run on your phone, and are almost always hot wallets. They tend to give you the most easy-to-use experience, but are less safe for bigger amount. Padawan wallet is an example of a mobile wallet.</string>
    <string name="t9_p8">4. Lighting wallet. The lightning network is a whole other topic not covered by Padawan. In general, the lightning network is an extension of what we can do with bitcoin, and is perfectly suited for smaller, faster transactions. Using a lightning wallet is a great way to manage day-to-day spending! We highly encourage looking into lightning wallet and payments as you make your way forward on your bitcoin journey!</string>
    <string name="t9_p9">5. Custodial wallets. Custodial wallets are wallets where the cryptographic keys do not reside on the device you use to receive/spend, but are rather held elsewhere under someone else\'s control. Your wallet then remotely asks the custodian too make payments on its behalf. This opens up other attack vectors (for example the custodian can decide to not abide by your requests for a transaction), but also makes the wallets easier to use and recover. In general, as your bitcoin experience grows and you get more comfortable with different types of wallets and use cases, you should prefer wallets that do not give up control of your keys, and custodial wallet should be considered a last resort option.</string>
</resources>
