<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="C6_title">Bitcoin units</string>
    <string name="C6_tagline">Satoshis, bitcoins, and beyond.</string>

    <string name="t6_p1">The word "bitcoin" has a few meanings. When referring to "bitcoin," people may mean the network, the protocol, or the open source project.</string>
    <string name="t6_p2">The word "bitcoin" also means one of the units of value when transacting on the Bitcoin network.</string>

    <string name="t6_h1">Breaking it down</string>
    <string name="t6_p3">Just like the kilometer can be broken down into meters and centimeters, a bitcoin can be broken into smaller parts.
</string>
    <string name="t6_p4">The most important units to describe bitcoin are the bitcoin and the satoshi. Sometimes we shorten the bitcoin unit to BTC and the satoshi unit to "sats".</string>

    <string name="t6_h2">Symbols</string>
    <string name="t6_p5">There is not yet an "official" symbol for either unit (bitcoin or satoshi). You may see the following symbols on Padawan or in other cryptocurrency exchanges or applications.</string>

    <string name="t6_h3">Which unit should I use?</string>
    <string name="t6_p6">We use the bitcoin (BTC) or satoshi (sat) units depending on the size of the transaction.</string>
    <string name="t6_p7">- A brand new car might be worth 1,700,000,000 sats, but it is more simple to say 1.7 bitcoin.</string>
    <string name="t6_p8">- You could buy a candy for 0.00000250 bitcoin, but it makes much more sense to say 250 satoshis.</string>
    <string name="t6_p9">Someone using bitcoin apps must develop the skill to understand both bitcoin and satoshi units. Many transactions are denominated in bitcoin, but their network fee (see tutorial #4) is almost always using the satoshi unit.</string>
    <string name="t6_p10">In the Padawan app, you can switch between the two units in the main wallet display page by touching the bitcoin/satoshi symbol.</string>
</resources>
