<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="E8_content">Recovering a wallet from a mnemonic is usually fairly easy. Menmonics use a standard called BIP39, which usually provides a common way to recover coins between different wallet implementations. The usual pattern for backing up and recovering a wallet is the following:\n
        1. We create a wallet and the software will provide us with either 12 or 24 words to write down and keep. The order of the words is important, so make sure you write them in the right order. In Padawan, you can see those 12 words at any time by going into the "Show Seed Phrase" screen. In most other wallet implementations, you will only get a chance to see those words once, SO MAKE SURE YOU WRITE THEM DOWN AND TREAT THEM LIKE THE MONEY THEY REPRESENT. Upon creating a new wallet, you can always try to send a tiny amount of bitcoin to the wallet, delete the wallet, and attempt a full recovery using the words provided by the wallet. If all goes well and you backed up your wallet correctly, you will be able to re-enter the same wallet and the coins will be there.\n\nIn Padawan, you\'d click on "I already have a Padawan wallet" and enter your 12 words mnemonic.\n\nThis ability to recover a wallet using only your words is very powerful, because it means that you don\'t actually need the wallet to be installed on your phone to transport your bitcoin; you can simply keep the 12 words somewhere safe (learning them by heart is also often useful, although you should not rely on that uniquely).\n\nThis aspect of bitcoin software is often misunderstood and is worth taking the time to appreciate; bitcoins are not "held" in any mobile or desktop wallet. They are simply accessed through them. But the testnet coins you have on Padawan can be recovered and used on a range of other mobile, desktop, and hardware wallets that support BIP39 bitcoin wallets. If your mnemonic words are properly backed up, deleting the app on your phone is not an issue at all!
    </string>
</resources>
