<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="E6_content">The action of sending a transaction over the bitcoin network and having that transaction be validated, confirmed and stored across thousands of computers over the world is immensely valuable; it\s also very costly.\n\nThe ability of the network to stay synchronized and distributed (which are properties important for further aspects that make it valuable, such as it\'s censorship-resistance and its apolitical nature) implies that the load that the network can take in terms of transactions per minute is limited. The leaner and lighter the load on the network, the more resistant it is to attacks, and the more neutral and robust it stays. This desire to stay lean comes in contrast with the demand for transactions by Bitcoin users, and the balance between the two is struck by having a limited amount of space for the total amount of bytes that can be transacted over the network per amount of time, yet allowing people to "bid" on that space.\n\nBecause the space is limited in terms of bytes per block (there is only 1 new block being mined every 10 minutes or so), bitcoin users compete for "space" on the blockchain by providing a fee for their transaction. The transactions with the highest fees are prioritized by the miners, and get included in the block they mine.
    </string>

    <string name="E7_content">Modern bitcoin wallets almost all use a process called <i>deterministic key generation</i>, where every new address is generated in a non-random fashion. This gives them the property of being very flexible in terms of generating new addresses (you\'ll notice that every bitcoin receive transaction uses a new address), while not having to remember them all (you do not have to make individual backups for all the addresses to which you received bitcoin). In fact the process looks a little bit like in the following diagram, where each "branch" of the tree is a process known in advance and shared across all bitcoin wallets:\n\nimage\n\nThe number of addresses that can be generated from this tree is infinite, yet because the process to generate new keys (the path the branches need to follow) is predetermined, the <i>only</i> necessary part of backing up such a "tree of addresses" is to remember the root of the tree!\n\nThe real word for this \"root\" of your wallet is the _wallet seed_. This wallet seed is simply a really, really big number, but numbers are notoriously hard to remember, and humans are usually really bad at writing them down properly without making mistakes or typos. Instead, a standard for how to encode these really big numbers has emerged in the bitcoin ecosystem. This standard uses a series of 12 or 24 words in a specific order, which together can always be used to recreate the wallet seed.\n\nPadawan uses this standard to allow users to create backups for its wallet. You\'ll find the 12 words (we call those your seedphrase) on a separate screen under the drawer options. Those words should be treated with the <i>utmost</i> care. They hold the key to all the bitcoin stored in a wallet.
    </string>

    <string name="E8_content">Recovering a wallet from a mnemonic is usually fairly easy. Menmonics use a standard called BIP39, which usually provides a common way to recover coins between different wallet implementations. The usual pattern for backing up and recovering a wallet is the following:\n
        1. We create a wallet and the software will provide us with either 12 or 24 words to write down and keep. The order of the words is important, so make sure you write them in the right order. In Padawan, you can see those 12 words at any time by going into the "Show Seed Phrase" screen. In most other wallet implementations, you will only get a chance to see those words once, SO MAKE SURE YOU WRITE THEM DOWN AND TREAT THEM LIKE THE MONEY THEY REPRESENT. Upon creating a new wallet, you can always try to send a tiny amount of bitcoin to the wallet, delete the wallet, and attempt a full recovery using the words provided by the wallet. If all goes well and you backed up your wallet correctly, you will be able to re-enter the same wallet and the coins will be there.\n\nIn Padawan, you\'d click on "I already have a Padawan wallet" and enter your 12 words mnemonic.\n\nThis ability to recover a wallet using only your words is very powerful, because it means that you don\'t actually need the wallet to be installed on your phone to transport your bitcoin; you can simply keep the 12 words somewhere safe (learning them by heart is also often useful, although you should not rely on that uniquely).\n\nThis aspect of bitcoin software is often misunderstood and is worth taking the time to appreciate; bitcoins are not "held" in any mobile or desktop wallet. They are simply accessed through them. But the testnet coins you have on Padawan can be recovered and used on a range of other mobile, desktop, and hardware wallets that support BIP39 bitcoin wallets. If your mnemonic words are properly backed up, deleting the app on your phone is not an issue at all!
    </string>
</resources>
