<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="C9_title">The different types of wallets</string>
    <string name="C9_tagline">Hot wallets, cold wallets, hardware wallets, mobile wallets… what you need to know!</string>

    <string name="t9_h1">Why is there more than one type of wallet?</string>
    <string name="t9_p1">A bitcoin wallet secures a set of cryptographic keys (very big and important numbers). It is important to protect these keys, and ensure they are not accessed by anyone other than the wallet owner.</string>
    <string name="t9_p2">There are many solutions for this requirement. Each type of wallet will have tradeoffs between its security level and its ease-of-use. Choosing the right wallet for a specific use can be overwhelming, but it is important! This chapter will help you understand why and when to use different types of bitcoin wallets.</string>

    <string name="t9_h2">Hot vs cold wallets</string>
    <string name="t9_p3">The first distinction between wallets is whether they have any access to the internet at all. \"Hot wallets\" are connected to the internet. Padawan is connected to the internet, and therefore is classified as a hot wallet. Hot wallet are more vulnerable to security attacks, and there are more ways they can fail, but it is much easier to send and receive transactions using them.</string>
    <string name="t9_p4">Think of a physical wallet you hold in your pocket with some cash in it. If it gets lost or stolen, you don\'t risk losing your savings, because those are held somewhere else safer (for example, in a bank account). A hot wallet is perfectly suited for holding small amounts of bitcoin for daily use (for example, the amount you would spend at a grocery store). It is easy to use, but you should not hold all your savings in it, since it is more vulnerable to attack and failure. On the other hand they\'re very handy! Knowing how much to keep on a hot wallet vs cold wallet is a good skill to develop, and often depends on your spending needs and habits.</string>
    <string name="t9_p5">\"Cold wallets\" are wallets that do not ever have access to the internet or the blockchain. They don\'t even know the internet exists! They are often specialized pieces of hardware that can perform a very small range of tasks, namely to sign bitcoin transactions with cryptographic keys they control. This makes them much more secure against attacks. It also means they are a bit more work when using them to spend or receive coins. Cold wallets are often used for storing larger amount of coins you don\'t need access to everyday, similar to how you might go to the bank to get money for the week.</string>

    <string name="t9_h3">Hardware, software, mobile, lightning, and custodial wallets</string>
    <string name="t9_p6">You might hear other names for wallets when searching for what best suits your needs. The following are commonly used by people to interact with bitcoin. Remember that a wallet can fit more than one of those categories.</string>
    <string name="t9_p7">1. Hardware wallets: these are often small, specialized bitcoin devices that can be plugged in a computer or phone, but cannot use the internet. They would be considered in the family of \"cold wallets\".</string>
    <string name="t9_p8">2. Software wallets: these often refer to applications you can use on your phone or desktop computer. Therefore, these are often hot wallets. It is not a very good name, because all bitcoin wallets use software! But you\'ll encounter the term often enough that you should know what it means.</string>
    <string name="t9_p9">3. Mobile wallets: these applications run on your phone, and are almost always hot wallets. They tend to give you the most easy-to-use experience, but are less safe for bigger amounts of bitcoin. Padawan wallet is an example of a mobile wallet.</string>
    <string name="t9_p10">4. Lighting wallets: the lightning network is a whole other topic not covered by Padawan. In summary, the Lightning Network is an extension of what we can do with bitcoin, and is perfectly suited for smaller, faster transactions. Using a lightning wallet is a great way to manage day-to-day spending. We highly encourage looking into lightning wallet and payments as you make your way forward on your bitcoin journey!</string>
    <string name="t9_p11">5. Custodial wallets: these are wallets where the cryptographic keys do not reside on the device you use to receive or spend, but are rather held elsewhere under someone else\'s control. Your wallet then remotely asks the custodian to make payments on your behalf. This opens up other attack vectors (for example the custodian can decide to not abide by your requests for a transaction, or potentially steal all your coins), but also makes the wallets easier to use and recover. In general, as your bitcoin experience grows and you get more comfortable with different types of wallets and use cases, you should prefer wallets that do not give up control of your keys, and the option of a custodial wallet should be considered a last resort.</string>
</resources>
